Klara's coming here next week.
Klara下个星期要到这里来.
Do we need a plan?
我们要计划一下吗?
What kind of plan?
什么计划?
How should we impress her?
我们应该怎样给她留下好印象?
We will impress her with our fine work.
我们要用我们出色的工作来给她留下深刻的印象.
Nancy, I used to say that when I worked with your husband and all the other lawyers in state government.
Nancy, 以前我与你丈夫以及州政府的其他律师共事时经常这么说.
But now, we are in the design business.
但现在, 我们经营的是设计行业.
It could use a facelift.
这房间可以整理一下.
Look what I found. Wow!
看我发现了什么. Wow!
I covered the chairs and moved the sofa in here.
我给椅子加了套子, 把沙发移了进来.
I picked up a new album for presenting our work.
我买了个新的影集来展现我们的作品.
Perfect.
太棒了.
Hello. You bought a what?
喂. 你买了什么?
We needed something here anyway.
反正我们这里还需要点东西.
I called Klara, confirmed the time, gave her directions and mailed her a map.
我给Klara打了电话, 确定了时间, 告诉她怎么走, 还给她寄了张地图.
Is there anything else we can do?
我们还能做点别的什么吗?
This is all very charming.
这一切太迷人了.
Who could that be?
可能是谁呢?
I'll get it. Excuse me.
我去开门. 失陪一会儿.
More tea, Klara?
再来点儿茶, Klara?
Yes. Thank you.
好的. 谢谢.
You know it's not easy being gracious these days.
你知道这年头做到殷勤有礼可不容易.
No, no, it isn't.
可不是嘛.
Aren't they gorgeous?
漂亮吗?
Who sent them?
是谁送的?
Let's see.
让我们看看.
"Thank you for making my home so beautiful.
"谢谢你们把我的房子装修得如此漂亮.
Best wishes, Janet Wu."
祝一切顺利, Janet Wu."
Janet Wu?
Just one of our many satisfied customers.
只是对我们的服务满意的许多顾客中的一位.
You were saying, Klara?
你刚才说什么来着, Klara?